Penny. Penny. Penny.
PENNY:
Oh, for God's sakes, I'm in the bathroom.
(Sheldon:)Shall I come back at a better time?
PENNY:
Get in here!
(Penny:)Hurry!
(Penny:)Don't you dare knock.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Penny:)I slipped in the shower.
I think I dislocated my shoulder.
(Sheldon:)Not surprising.
(Sheldon:)You have no safety mat
or adhesive stickers...
(Sheldon:)...to allow for purchase on a surface
with a low coefficient of static friction.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)Tubs are slippery.
(Penny:)I know. I slipped.
(Sheldon:)I have a series of whimsical duck stickers
on the bottom of my tub.
(Penny:)Whatever. Will you just
turn the water off and help me up?
SHELDON: They're holding umbrellas.
-Unh.
(Penny:)-What?
-The ducks in my tub.
Unh. Uh-huh.
(Sheldon:)They're whimsical,
because ducks have neither a need for...